(Bernadette:)He's so little. I'm sure it's fine.
How can it be fine?
(Howard:)I just got attacked by a clearly
anti-Semitic wild animal.
(Leonard:)It's not what we planned,
but this isn't so bad, right?
(Penny:)It is freaking amazing.
(Leonard:)Well, glad
you're feeling better.
(Penny:)I was just hungry and cranky,
(Penny:)and I've never been called
"ma'am" before.
(Leonard:)Is that a big deal?
(Penny:)Kind of. When was the first time
someone called you "sir"?
(Leonard:)Sixth grade,
(Leonard:)but I wore a sport coat
and carried a briefcase, so...
(Penny:)Can you believe
when I met you I was 22?
(laughs)
I mean, it's crazy!
(Penny:)Where did all that time go?
(Leonard:)Mm, you watched
The Bachelor a lot.
(Penny:)Yeah, go ahead and make jokes,
(Penny:)but your thirties
are almost over.
(Leonard:)No, they're not.
(Penny:)You're closer to 40
than you are 30.
Ha, ha! You
married an old man.
(Leonard:)Tell you what.
(Leonard:)Let's do something
fun tonight.
(Penny:)Won't make us any younger.